[{"answer": "It's been very difficult, Piers.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "How are you and the family bearing up since Amy died?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "I have.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Have you been taken aback by the sheer scale of the reaction to her death?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "I think all of those.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "How would you describe how you've been feeling since you heard the news?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "I was in New York.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Where were you when you heard the news?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "She was on her own.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "She was on her own?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "I -- I had incredible clarity.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "What was your reaction immediately?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Did a part of you expect this call one day?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Well, alcohol was a different issue.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "What about alcohol?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "No, I really don't.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "But do you have any sort of concrete regrets, things you wish you'd done?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "I mean, I have moments when I just can't believe what's happened.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Have you had moments in private where you've really lost it about this or have you been able to keep things together?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Do you think she ever really committed to rehab properly or not?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Well, there's so many stories.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "What was the moment for you when you thought, OK, wow, this is interesting?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Well, Sylvia will say -- Sylvia will say that she wasn't expelled, but she was actually expelled.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "And the irony was that she actually left the Sylvia Young school because she wasn't, in their eyes, performing academically well enough, right?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "We were -- at Sylvia Young, she met a guy called Tyler James, who was a great friend.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "When she left Sylvia, what was the moment for you that you realized this little girl of yours was going to be an international star?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Not really, no.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "You hadn't seen it coming?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Well, I'd like to say me, of course, but the truth is that Janice, my ex-wife's family, there were professional musicians on that side, too.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Where do you think she'd got that from?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Was that how you saw it?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "An incredible force for good in her life.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "A force for good in her life?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "My immediate reaction was that he was a very charming guy.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "When she first got together with this guy, as her father, what was your immediate reaction when you saw the kind of person that he was?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "I was suspicious of his motivation, yes, I was.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "So you were suspicious of his motivation, really?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know about ecstasy, but cocaine and heroin, yes, I do.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Do you believe that?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Oh, frequently, and his family.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Did you ever confront him?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Leave my daughter alone, leave us alone.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "What would you say?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Did they not believe that he had got Amy into these hard drugs?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Well, yes, I did.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Do you fear that, you know, you were going to wake up one day with the terrible news that you eventually did, ironically at a time when she was a lot cleaner, but did you fear through that period with Blake that this was all going to end horribly?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Yes, but she was a headstrong girl.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "But of course, Amy, at the time, thought, what's all the fuss about?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "But, you know, I would imagine fabulously successful, very rich, and probably a little part of her was thinking, hey, dad, back off, this is my life, right?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "So I believe.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "But he provided the platform for her to take those drugs?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "You could do, but you know, I think I love Lisa, she loved Blake and Blake loved her in his own way.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Could you know?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "No, I wouldn't talk to him.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Have you talked to him since she died?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "He says he has, but he hasn't.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Has he made any attempt to contact you?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "He hasn't written to you or anything?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "That's a fair point.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "What do you say to people who criticize you like that?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Well, I was concerned, but we had, I could draw her on the experiences that we had with the recovery from the drugs.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Did you feel it was a genuine one, or were you still very concerned?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Well, it clearly was.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Was the Achilles' heel alcohol in the end?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Well, alcohol is far more dangerous than drugs are anyway.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "But how bad an addiction was that for her after the drugs?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "She had started drinking, yes.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Had she been drinking alone the night she died?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Do you know how much she had that night?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "There was alcohol in her system, yes.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "But it would appear that she had been drinking alcohol?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "We're still -- we know it's not drugs, but we don't know the official coroner's verdict.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "And do you know what actually killed her?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Well, my instinct is that it's pretty much what the doctor warned us about.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Do you have any instinct?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "When the tour was booked, it was booked -- I mean, obviously, these things are booked nine months previously.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "What happened in Belgrade, do you think?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Well, it helps disadvantaged children, young adults.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Who does it help?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Well, the easiest way is to go on WWW.AmyWinehouseFoundation.Co.UK and donate.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "What's the easiest way to do that?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Well, the great memories are seeing her on stage for the first time, but my great memories, the last -- I went away on the Friday to New York, as I say, I had a show the following Monday at the Blue Note.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "Either professionally or personally, or both?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "We were.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "I mean, you must miss her terribly, right?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Her legacy will be her music, hopefully there will be -- hopefully there will be some more music.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "What do you hope her legacy will be, Mitch?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "She was one of the greatest talents I've ever seen.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Her foundation is going to help thousands and thousands of children, and what better legacy could you want than that?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "For a moment, I thought it was just too -- a car and a motorcycle on fire until I got to the scene where my wife was already there.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "What went through your mind?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "At first, when I saw it was a fire, an accident, I didn't think about myself.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "When you look back at the video, what do you think now?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Um, I don't -- I don't think hero, like, would be like the word to describe the people who were like trying to help lifting the car, or helping the person, I mean Brandon.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "I mean, do you consider yourselves to be heroes?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "James, Anvar, Abbass, I think you are all heroes as well as everyone who helped to that scene.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "He is still in the Intensive Care Unit at a hospital in Salt Lake City, which is about 90 miles south of Logan, but they are hoping to move him out of that unit later today and move him into a regular patient room, where they will upgrade him to the condition of satisfactory.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "And Tyler, can you tell me, what is Brandon's -- clarify what Brandon's condition is please, Tyler?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "He has actually did see the video earlier today during some news coverage, and he -- that was the first time that he had seen it, and he was shocked by it.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Is he aware of the video?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "I think that he thinks that they were all -- they were all heroes.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "And what was -- what was his view, do you think, of the people that saved his life?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "I'm not kind of surprise.", "docId": "110913pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "What is your reaction?", "qSentId": 653}]